Have you guys heard about
this research team...
...that's trying to transgenically manipulate
chicken DNA...
_to create some sort of chicken dinosaur?
I think that sounds wonderful.
What?
You're afraid of both dinosaurs and chickens.
Yes, but tell me a dinosaur-chicken salad
sandwich wouldn't hit the Mesozoic spot.
[LAUGHING]
-Hey, guys.
-Hello.
-We still on for tomorrow night?
-Yeah. I'm excited to meet your girlfriend.
Speaking of which, according to
a recent study out of Oxford University...
...when someone takes on
a new romantic partner...
...that person loses one or two close friends.
Since when do you read social science?
I go to the bathroom like everybody else.
Why would I lose friends
just because I started dating?
You didn't lose any when you met Amy.
Well, no, the study refers
to romantic partners.
Not the way
I would categorize the two of us.
-But you guys kiss and hold hands.
-I've seen them do it. It's not romantic.
Look, I'm not the kind of guy who drops
his friends just because he's in a relationship.
-What happens if she doesn't like us?
-Well, hey, you're my dear friends.
You'll get a Christmas card for a couple
of years and then you're dead to me.
So, Howard, is Stuart
still living with your mom?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
-But he's going to.
My mom got him cable!
My whole life growing up in that house,
no cable.
Do you know how many HBOs
that leech had my mother get him? Seven.
Seven HBOs. Seven.
Long story short, they have seven HBOs.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-Hey, guys.
-Hello.
-Emily, you know most everybody.
-Hi.
-This is Leonard. This is Penny.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to finally meet you too.
-Hi.
Hello.
Wow, Raj, you were not lying about her.
I told you she exists.
I hear you're a dermatologist.
Yeah, I'm a resident at Huntington Hospital.
Oh! I like their emergency room.
Even if it turns out you don't have dengue
fever, they still let you take a lollipop.
You know, Penny just started training
to be a pharmaceutical sales rep.
-Maybe she could practice on you sometime.
- It would be great to practice on a real doctor.
Yeah, I'm sure that'd be fine.
I have some odd freckles on my buttocks.
Can I make an appointment
for you to look at them?
Um, okay, I guess.
I'm with him three years, nothing. She's with
him two minutes and he's taking his pants off.
Last night was fun.
What'd you think of Emily?
I don't know. I kind of got
the sense she didn't like me.
Did she say she didn't like you?
Of course not. No one says
they don't like you straight to your face.
We have led different lives.
You guys just met.
Why would she feel that way?
It's just this vibe I got.
-I'm sure you're worried about nothing.
-Probably right.
I used to think my PE teacher didn't like me,
but it turned out she liked me a little too much.
-Really?
-Yeah, it was fine.
We went to a Melissa Etheridge concert,
I got an A, it all worked out.
When you go to Emily's office to practice
you'll see it's fine.
Yeah, I hope you're right.
You really went your entire life without anyone
saying, "I hate you," to your face?
Yeah.
I'd say it now, but look at those cheekbones.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
I miss Stuart's place.
All this loud music and exposed brick.
Is this a comic book store
or a rave at the third little pig's house?
Yeah, I wish Stuart would reopen,
I hate this place too.
Okay, him I believe because he's an
80-year-old man in a 15-year-old's T-shirt.
You're just upset about Stuart
and your mom and all their HBOs.
Yes, I am. You know, I can't even watch
Game of Thrones now. ..
...without thinking of my mother saying:
[IMITATING HIS MOTHER]
"Stuart, which one is Thrones?"
He might not reopen. He didn't get a lot
of money from the insurance company.
Oh, boy, if there's one thing that gets my goat,
it's those dad-gum insurance companies.
Why, because they won't get off your lawn?
Is Stuart trying to get a loan
or find investors?
All I know is he's got my mother
buying four-ply toilet paper.
I mean, four-ply.
If his butt is so delicate
why doesn't he just use an angora rabbit?
For starters, they shed and bite.
Hey, here's a thought. Why don't we put up
the rest of the money that Stuart needs”?
So we'd be, like, owners
of a comic book store?
Kind of a dream come true.
It does sound fun.
Maybe we could come up with a business plan
to compete with this place.
I'll give you a plan right now.
Step one, open comic book store.
Step two, start rumor this comic book store
gives you genital warts.
Step three, buy a big bag
to put the money in.
It's not that bad.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Thanks for letting me practice
my sales pitch on you. I really appreciate it.
-Sure.
- I brought coffee.
I wasn't sure what you like so I got a regular,
a cappuccino and a chai tea.
Since you like Raj,
I thought you might be into that.
Thanks. If we could get started,
I'm a little busy.
Yeah, sure, let me just get out my materials.
Leonard gave me this.
He used to carry it around in high school.
You can still see the dent
where they whacked him with it.
Ahem. Okay, I would like to talk to you about
our new birth-control pill, Femivra.
Great.
So Femivra's triphasic design
provides balanced hormonal exposure.
All right.
It has also been shown to cause significantly
fewer side effects than other oral contraceptives.
Although it can cause acne.
Which, if you ask me, kind of increases
its effectiveness as a contraceptive.
Funny.
Okay, I'm sorry, did we get off
on the wrong foot?
Since the other night, I feel like
you might have a problem with me.
No, it's fine.
Are you sure”? Because it doesn't seem fine.
Okay, if you really wanna talk about this...
-...| do have a problem.
-Oh, my God. Tell me. What did I do?
Look, it's nothing, it's just Raj told me
that a while ago you two hooked up.
What? Why would he say that?
Did it not happen?
Well, I wouldn't exactly call it a hookup.
-Did you kiss?
-Yeah.
Were you naked?
Yeah.
-So it was a hookup.
-No.
Yeah.
So, what are some ways we can set our
comic book store apart from the competition?
Kids buy comic books. It'd be great
to figure out a way to get more kids in.
You know, when I was a kid I loved
going there, but I could never get a ride.
Ooh, what if we got a van
and drove around and picked kids up?
Nice.
Like at parks and schools.
Toy stores, puppet shows.
Hold on, so your idea is to get a van and cruise
the streets looking for kids to pick up?
Yes.
And are you gonna use candy
to lure them in?
We are now.
You told Emily we hooked up?
Uh, well, in my defense, I tell everybody.
Why would you say that?
We had a conversation about past lovers.
We weren't lovers, didn't sleep together.
We got drunk and fooled around.
Why couldn't you leave me out of it?
We were being honest.
You'd leave me out of a conversation
with the next guy if you dump Leonard?
-Why say it?
Yes.
Well, I would never leave you off my list.
And not just because without you we're playing
fast and loose with the word "list."
Well, good job, now she hates me.
Great.
On the bright side, that Oxford study was right.
One friend down.
I wonder who you're going to lose next.
You, okay? It's you. You're next.
No, you're crazy about me.
I don't know what Emily's so upset about.
Even if I had slept with him, so what?
Everyone has a past.
-Ahem.
-Almost everyone has a past.
Come on, look how pretty you are.
I'm sure this isn't the first girl to hate you.
It's not.
And |I'm sure you can turn it around.
How? You can't force someone to like you.
What if you just hang around and act
like her friend until you wear her down?
I mean, next thing you know, you're in her
home, eating her food, drinking her wine.
-No, that won't work.
-You're right. Cheers.
I know. Why don't you use your sales training
to go back down there and sell yourself?
-What?
BERNADETTE: Yeah.
But instead of selling a drug,
you'd be selling Penny.
-It's cute.
-It's stupid.
Well, maybe people would like you more
if you didn't crap all over their ideas.
I'm gonna go with Penny on this one.
Then again, why wouldn't I?
I mean, we go way back.
Oh, my God. I didn't used to like you.
Shh. Amy's here now. Shh.
The more I think about it, the more intrigued
I am about having our own store.
We'll get to see all the new stuff
before it hits the shelves.
And we'll get to have fun interactions
with our customers.
"This isn't a library. Buy it or get out.”
You say things like that all the time.
Yes, but as an owner, I'll finally have a good
comeback to, "You don't work here, shut up.”
Do you know how Penny told Raj
he should have left her off his list?
Yeah.
Think when she and I had that conversation
she left people off hers?
I'm sure she did.
Why?
Because if she hadn't,
she'd still be wading through the list.
Will you stay out of this?
Heh. If only Penny had said that
once in a while.
What difference does it make?
You're the one she wants to marry.
-That's true.
-I'm not sure...
...that complete honesty
is always the best thing for a relationship.
Yeah, he's right.
Once, in a moment of candor...
...| told Amy that her hair
reminded me of a duck caught in an oil spill.
She stormed out.
Which was sad,
because we were playing Scrabble...
...and I had all the letters
to spell "persimmon.”
Why are you even part of this conversation?
You don't know anything about women.
I know that if I had a wife or a fiancée. ..
...I'd ask her first
before I invested money in a comic book store.
[SIGHS]
-He's right.
-Well, of course I am.
I was also right about her hair.
It did everything but quack.
Hey, there's something
I wanted to run past you.
What's up?
Well, the guys and I were thinking about
investing in Stuart's comic book store.
|s that okay?
Why are you asking me?
Well, we're engaged
and it's kind of a big deal financially.
Seems like something we should talk about.
Oh.
Well, would you consider mounds of credit
card debt kind of a big deal financially?
LEONARD:
Yeah.
PENNY:
Huh.
So me and the guys were talking
about this great investment opportunity--
Nope.
But you didn't hear what it was.
I know.
Oh, come on.
-Fine. What is it?
-It's to help reopen the comic book store.
Nope.
Hear me out.
Howie, you know we're saving up
for a house.
I know, but all the guys are doing it.
We're splitting it four ways
so it's really not that much money.
Just seems like a risky investment.
I get that.
Okay, look.
The real reason this is important is...
[CLEARS THROAT]
...before my dad left me and my mom...
...he used to take me
to the comic book store.
It was one of the few things we did together.
Howie, I had no idea.
Well, I don't like to talk about it.
Oh, baby.
That story's made-up, isn't it?
That's how much buying
a comic book store means to me.
I'd like your honest opinion on something.
Of course.
Now, before I start, I need you to know
that I'm very excited about this.
And anything you say
that isn't enthusiastically supportive...
...will throw our entire relationship
into question.
So keep an open mind.
I'm feeling a little backed into a corner,
Sheldon.
Perfect.
Now, I'm considering investing
in Stuart's comic book store.
Interesting.
Can you see how a grown man,
an accomplished scientist...
...who invests in a store that sells picture
books about flying men in colorful underwear...
...might be wasting both his financial
and intellectual resources?
No.
Then I think it's a terrific idea.
Great.
Wait till you hear about our van.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-Hey. Thanks for inviting us over.
-Hi. Thank you for coming.
Listen, Penny, before you start...
...I wanna apologize for being so rude
the other day in my office.
-No, no. No need to apologize.
-Excuse me, can I say something?
I just love both you guys
and I want you to get along.
And when I say "love," I meant as a friend.
And, uh, we're too soon, right?
Okay, sit down. Listen, Emily...
...what happened between me and Raj
was a long time ago.
I made it seem like
a bigger deal than I should have.
Yeah. And Leonard and I are engaged now.
And I'm just hoping
we can put this whole thing behind us.
I'd like that too.
Yeah, I thought I'd be okay with it,
but then I saw how pretty you are.
Oh. That's so sweet.
I mean, look at you, you are gorgeous.
It's true, you're both gorgeous.
Kind of says something about the man
who could bed you both.
[CHUCKLES]
You get why I've been alone
most of my adult life.
So, what brings you by?
Well, I don't need a reason, it's my house.
Technically it's your mom's house,
but we certainly want you to feel welcome.
I'm always welcome.
Just try and call first.
Okay, let's get down to business.
Howie was thinking about putting up
some money to help reopen the store...
...but before that happens,
I have a few questions.
I appreciate the offer, but actually,
your mother already gave me the money.
What?
Yeah. I told her it was too much, but she said
she was happy to help out her bubala.
[CHUCKLES]
Excuse me.
Ma, you are canceling that check...
...and Stuart is not your bubala, I'm your
bubala, you can't have more than one bubala!
I don't know who he's talking to,
she's at Target buying me shirts.
I'm so glad we could work this all out.
Yeah, me too.
We should have dinner
with you and Leonard.
-We would love that.
-Great.
-Okay, good night, guys.
-All right, night.
Bye.
BOTH:
I hate her.
I'm disappointed we're not gonna have
our own comic book store.
I was looking forward to it.
Would have been nice
to have a place that's ours.
Where we could just sit
and read comics in peace.
With comfy seats.
And snacks.
I guess it was too good to be true.
Yeah.
[ALL SIGH]
[English - US - SDH]